1: Transfer Points
2: Escape From
the Culling Game
3: Passage In and
Out of Colonies
4: Communication In
and Out of Colonies
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Episode 59
Sendai Colony
Festering Life Sword
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Don't Move
The Sun, Moon, and Stars Squad was
the Fujiwara Clan's personal squad of assassins.
We lived in darkness and served with selfless devotion.
We were even forbidden from having our own names.
Yet that man once granted me a name.
So he could execute me instead
for his crime of slaying his own kin.
Let's let it all out!
Through the transfer of Ishigori Ryu
and Uro Takako's points,
Okkotsu Yuta came to possess 190 points.
To Be Continued